<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on My Blog</title><link>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on My Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 09:39:15 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automate your game builds in Github with GameCI and Github Actions</title><link>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/github-actions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 09:39:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/github-actions/</guid><description>Building Unity projects are relatively quick and consistent, but most of the time this renders your computer unusable until it is complete, thankfully we have GameCI to the rescue. For this article I will showcase how I used GameCI and Github Actions in order to help me and my teammates develop our game Get Guns, Go Grapple.
As always, to get a better understanding of the tools presented in this article, I recommend reading the documentation for each tool if available.</description></item><item><title>Building Aseprite from source without using Visual Studio for Windows</title><link>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/building-aseprite/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 20:56:13 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/building-aseprite/</guid><description>Aseprite is a pixel-art tool to create 2D animations, sprites, and any kind of graphics for games. Aseprite usually costs 449.95 pesos on Steam, but it is actually free if you build it yourself from source.
I will mostly be following their install guide, and while this is good, I found it confusing the first time so I hope this will help streamline the process.
Dependencies To compile Aseprite on Windows, you would need the following:</description></item><item><title>Setting up my computer for game development in Unity</title><link>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/vscode-with-unity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 04:11:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/vscode-with-unity/</guid><description>Hello, in this post I will show how I set up my computer for game development in Unity. This would involve the installation of the Unity game engine, .NET Core and .NET Framework for the dependencies, Visual Studio Code as my text editor/IDE.
Do take note that while these instructions are made in Windows 10, it should be pretty much the same for other operating systems.
Installing Unity Installing Unity is pretty straightforward.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 09:00:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>Hi, my name is Jolo. I am currently a game development student residing in the Philippines. I mostly make games in Unity, but I also tend to check out other tech in my free time.
In this site, I plan to document the things I use and find interesting, as well as post stuff about my projects down the line.
Aside from game development, in my free time I play video games (obviously), read manga, watch vtubers, and learn more about tech both in hardware and software.</description></item></channel></rss>