<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on ReadLine</title><link>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on ReadLine</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 22:50:50 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automate your development with Github Actions</title><link>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/github-actions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 22:50:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/github-actions/</guid><description>Github Actions So what is Github Actions anyway? Basically, it is a set of instructions that gets run on a computer depending on what has happened in your repository. You can generate a documentation site for your code, run shell scripts to use with your project, or even make a build of your project, and that is just what I used during the development of our thesis game Get Guns, Go Grapple.</description></item><item><title>Setting up my computer for game development in Unity</title><link>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/vscode-with-unity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 04:11:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/vscode-with-unity/</guid><description>Hello, in this post I will show how I set up my computer for game development in Unity. This would involve the installation of the Unity game engine, .NET Core and .NET Framework for the dependencies, Visual Studio Code as my text editor/IDE.
Do take note that while these instructions are made in Windows 10, it should be pretty much the same for other operating systems.
Installing Unity Installing Unity is pretty straightforward.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 09:00:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://bulletproofpancake.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>Hi, my name is Jolo. I am currently a game development student residing in the Philippines. I mostly make games in Unity, but I also tend to check out other tech in my free time.
In this site, I plan to document the things I use and find interesting, as well as post stuff about my projects down the line.
Aside from game development, in my free time I play video games (obviously), read manga, watch vtubers, and learn more about tech both in hardware and software.</description></item></channel></rss>